MONA Jiravirotekul

Email: cooleye4@yahoo.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mona-jiravirotekul-26347768/ Portfolio: https://monaesthetician.github.io/ | Github: https://github.com/monaesthetician| Cell: (513) 429-6322

Entry level Web Developer

Experienced in marketing and sales more than 10 years. Eager to learn new things, used to assist graphic designers to accomplish work before deadlines. Self-motivated web development and seeking an opportunity to support the team to succeed.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- Git-hub
- React-Redux

- Microsoft Office
- M.E.R.N Stack
- HTML5

- CSS3
- SQL
- MongoDB

Experience

April 2017- Present

Server, Ban Thai Restaurant

Cincinnati, Ohio

- Provide excellent customer services.
- Greet customers and presents menus.
- Make suggestions based on their preference.
- Take and serve food/drinks orders.
- Up-sell when appropriate.
- Arrange table settings.
- Keep tables and dining room clean and tidy at all times.
- Deliver checks and collect payments.

•

January 2013 - July 2014 Account Executive, Money channel

Bangkok, Thailand

- Assisting in the development of sales presentations and marketing materials.
- Developed and manage revenue producing relationships with client and agencies.
- Provided consultation to sales managers, sales teams and clients.
- Provided clients with convergent selling, to package several broadcast and online products.
- Other responsibilities as assigned by manager.

June 2011 - March 2013 Retail Sales Associate, King power

Bangkok, Thailand

- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Assisting customers with finding alternative merchandise to meet needs.
- Organized racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers and promote specific merchandise.
- Participating company training opportunities as the company offers.

April 2004 - September 2008 Account Exec

Account Executive, Q Advertising F

Bangkok, Thailand

- Sold print advertising.
- Worked positively and productively with the production team and finance department to provide clients and agencies satisfaction.
- Worked independently and collaboratively with multiple departments (internally & externally) to ensure opportunities for revenue growth are maximized.
- Worked collaboratively with internal partners to drive revenue.
- Followed all station procedures for preparing orders, resolving billing issues, submitting regular reports regarding sales, forecasts and competitive analysis.

April 2001 - August 2004 Customer Service, Inspire Image Bangkok, Thailand

- Obtained client information by answering telephone calls; interviewing clients; verifying information.
- Established policies by entering client information to requirements.
- Informed clients by explaining procedures; answering questions; providing information.
- Maintained communication equipment by reporting problems.
- Maintained and improves quality results by adhering to standards; recommending improved procedures.
- Updated job knowledge by studying new product

Education

Kable Academy • March - June 2021

Web Development

Aveda Fedric's Institute • February 2020 - August 2021

Esthiology

Waltham Forest College • 2014-2015

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Westminster Kingsway College • 2015-2016

English for Speaker of Other Languages (ESOL)

Bachelors of arts • Sripatum University • 1995 - 1999

Communication arts, Advertising

Cincinnati, Ohio

Cincinnati, Ohio

London, UK

London, UK

Bangkok, Thailand